Chicago! I'm Ryan O'Connell! And this is my
sister Cassidy! And we are The Stardust
Angels!
We were looking for a signal A light in the
endless black A single voice in the universe to
tell us we're on the right track. We found the
fire in the white shadows. We found the heart in
the machine. Building a dream from nothing.
Sound the world has never seen. We are the
starter's engine. Racin' through the night,
we're burnin' on the fuel of a brand new light.
Start our stand, yeah. Yeah, we're takin'
flight. Turnin' our future on. Shinin' so
bright.
They tried to ground us, keep us small, tell us
that we were gonna fall. But they don't know the
things we know. They haven't seen the places
we'll go. We had the smallest of fortune. We had
the small, but saddest of all. But they don't
know the things we know They haven't seen the
places we'll go We are the start of a stage, yeah
We're racing through the night We're burning on
the fuel of a brand new light
Start of a stage, yeah Yeah, we're taking flight
Turning our future on
Shining so bright
We are the cosmos. We are the fire. We're taking
this one higher and higher. We are the stardust.
We are the engine. We are the stardust
engine. We are the stardust engine.
Yeah, we're taking flight
Turning our future on Shining so bright Taking
flight Thank you!